<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Robert-Jensen.dk</title>
    <link>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Robert-Jensen.dk</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 13:20:37 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.robert-jensen.dk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Using Github Actions to Build Containers (and host them)</title>
      <link>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2021-using-github-actions-to-build-containers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 13:20:37 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2021-using-github-actions-to-build-containers/</guid>
      <description>Some time ago, I wrote a blog, around how to easily build and host, Docker containers using Dockers autobuild tools.
After the blog post Docker both changed to using rate limits, for API calls, but also removed the Autobuild feature.
I understand fully, that Docker is trying to find out, how to make money, but I am not a fan of the Rate limit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello Buildpacks, goodbye Dockerfiles</title>
      <link>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2021-hello-buildpacks-goodbye-dockerfiles/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 13:55:17 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2021-hello-buildpacks-goodbye-dockerfiles/</guid>
      <description>I might be late to the party, but recently I learned about Buildpacks.io and what they can do vs Dockerfiles, and I just had to try it out.
If you never heard about Buildpacks, then it&amp;rsquo;s a way to package your application into a container, without using Dockerfiles.
The benefits can be</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disable Windows Print Spooler to avoid Exploit CVE-2021-1675</title>
      <link>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2021-disable-print-spooler-exploit/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 19:42:06 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2021-disable-print-spooler-exploit/</guid>
      <description>Update 7.7.2021 : There is now a patch avaliable. Please patch your systems, and only use this blog post, as a reference, on how to do configuration management, on multiple systems. And not as a way to fix this problem. https://msrc.microsoft.com/update-guide/vulnerability/CVE-2021-34527
A new exploit, allowing remote code execution on Windows servers using the Print spoller service, has been released as CVE-2021-1675.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Auto Install Cloudbase-Init</title>
      <link>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2021-auto-install-cloudbase-init/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2021 11:27:40 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2021-auto-install-cloudbase-init/</guid>
      <description>Ever since vRealize Automation 8 was released, and we started using Cloud-Init, I have been looking at installing CloudBase-Init for Windows as well, as part of my automated Packer template deployment.
While Cloud-Init on Linux, is dead simple to install, the Windows version, has given me a lot of problems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Level Up, as a vSphere admin</title>
      <link>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2021-vmug-level-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 10:58:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2021-vmug-level-up/</guid>
      <description>For the Danish VMUG summermeeting, on the 2 June 2021, I had the pleasure of presenting, &amp;ldquo;How to level up, as a vSphere admin&amp;rdquo;.
A presentation, around what tools/technologies, to look at, if you are doing infrastructure today, to prepare, for the future.
This post, will be published, during the presentation, as part of the last demo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install Loginsight agent using SaltStack</title>
      <link>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2021-install-loginsight-agent-using-saltstack/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 20:50:06 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2021-install-loginsight-agent-using-saltstack/</guid>
      <description>For a POC i&amp;rsquo;m preparing for, I had the chance to look at bit more at SaltStack.
I like the product, and what it can do, but I really need a usecase, to do anything usefull with it. It&amp;rsquo;s the same with many other products, but with SaltStack, i&amp;rsquo;m just feeling it more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Project</title>
      <link>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2021-new-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 20:13:49 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2021-new-project/</guid>
      <description>I love doing doing Crossfit, and before Covid19 hit, I was pretty active in my local Box.
Crossfit boxes are split into 2 segments. The official affiliates, which is a part of the company Crossfit.com, and all the others, which offer functional training.
For a new person, that wants to get into shape, and do some functinal training, then it&amp;rsquo;s probably hard to see the difference.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Integrate Azure Devops With Vmware Codestream</title>
      <link>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2021-integrate-azure-devops-with-vmware-codestream/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 08:22:25 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2021-integrate-azure-devops-with-vmware-codestream/</guid>
      <description>For a customer case, I had to show integration between Azure Devops, and VMware CodeStream.
Since the Git endpoint in Code Stream, does not work with Azure DevOps Git repository, I had to find another way of doing the integration.
The solution was quite simple. Trigger the pipeline, using a pipeline run by Azure Devops.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keeping .env files in sync using Bitwarden</title>
      <link>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2021-env-files-and-bitwarden/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 10:48:02 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2021-env-files-and-bitwarden/</guid>
      <description>Update : After posting this, I was told that Grand Orchard, had already written a similar post, around how to do the same, using 1Password.
So if you are a 1Password user, then take a look at his blog
 I use multiple computers, and sometimes it can be hard, to keep everything in sync.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When Testing Got Easy - a story about SMTP and Docker</title>
      <link>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2021-when-testing-got-easy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 15:55:59 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2021-when-testing-got-easy/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes it&amp;rsquo;s the simple tings, that are the hardest. For a small projekt, i&amp;rsquo;m working on, I have to test sending a lot of emails. A simple thing, but in my case, I don&amp;rsquo;t have a local SMTP server.
I could set one up, but then, I have to configure users, maybe MX records, and other stuff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installing Harbor Container Registry Behind Traefik Reverse Proxy With Let&#39;s Encrypt Certificate</title>
      <link>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2021-harbor-behind-traefik-with-letsencrypt-certificate/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 13:53:10 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2021-harbor-behind-traefik-with-letsencrypt-certificate/</guid>
      <description>Ever since Docker enforced their rate limit, I have been looking at using some other registry, to put my containers, but also to use as a proxy, so I hit the Docker api a blit less.
Everywhere I look, Harbor is mentioned, so that is the one, that I have been looking at.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easy Updating CI/CD Tools</title>
      <link>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2021-easy-updating-cdicd-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 09:18:30 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2021-easy-updating-cdicd-tools/</guid>
      <description>Update 09/06/2021 : Docker has changed their licenses, so that AutoBuild, in no longer part of the free license., due to it being exploided by Bitcoin miners. A shame, but something i fully understand. Update 23/03/2021 : I have changed my container image, to be build using Gitlab, and pushed to my private Harbor registry, due to speed, and amount of pulls.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Remote Access to Demolab using Apache Guacamole</title>
      <link>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2021-remote-access-to-demolab/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2021 09:35:55 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2021-remote-access-to-demolab/</guid>
      <description>My demolab, is not hostet at home, but remote. So i&amp;rsquo;m always dependend, on some kind of remote access. At home, I use a IPSEC Site2Site VPN, between my PFsense, and the Edgerouter lite, I have in my Demo enviroment.
Remote I use Tailscale for client VPN, as I have described, in an earlier post.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tailscale on Ubitique Edgerouter</title>
      <link>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2021-tailscale-on-edgerouter/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 20:28:10 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2021-tailscale-on-edgerouter/</guid>
      <description>Update 06.08.2021 : Updated blog to version 1.12.3 - Tested and working. 30.01.2021 : Updated blog to version 1.4.1 - Tested and working.
Tailscale is what I have been using, to get access to my demo enviroment, and allow clients to communicate with each other, across networks etc. But I have really missed, having it installed on my firewall, to make it act as a more traditional vpn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Secure Deployments With Docker, Traefik and Let&#39;s Encrypt</title>
      <link>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2021-secure-deployments-with-docker-and-traefik/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2021 20:45:52 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2021-secure-deployments-with-docker-and-traefik/</guid>
      <description>During the christmas holliday, I had some time, to look into Traefik reverse proxy.
The reason for me to use Traefik, is due to the automation, it delivers. It can automaticly detect deployments, and present them, and for my demo projects, that is exactly what I need.
Optimal, I would deploy everything to a K8S cluster, but i&amp;rsquo;m having some problems getting it working with Traefik.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Custom DNS Resolver for Homelabs</title>
      <link>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2020-custom-dns-resolver-for-homelabs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Dec 2020 09:53:39 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2020-custom-dns-resolver-for-homelabs/</guid>
      <description>Using custom dns servers, depending on enviroment, or resolving multiple internal domains, can be a real pain.
You can setup host files, but it&amp;rsquo;s a pain to manage. You can also setup your own DNS server, but if you are using company VPN etc, then it&amp;rsquo;s not always the right DNS server, that is being used.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Giving Back for the First Time</title>
      <link>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2020-giving-back-for-the-first-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Dec 2020 15:18:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2020-giving-back-for-the-first-time/</guid>
      <description>One thing, I have been wanting to do, ever since I started learning Python, and started using Github, was to give back, the the projects, that I use. I remember reading, how to get started doing this, but I see myself as a beginner, when it comes to coding, and find myself thinking, &amp;ldquo;why would anybody want something, that I have done.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Application Deployment With Salt and Vra</title>
      <link>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2020-application-deployment-with-salt-and-vra/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2020 14:09:39 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2020-application-deployment-with-salt-and-vra/</guid>
      <description>Here is a short post, around my first integration between SaltStack and vRealize Automation.
Expect this to be updated, as I get more experience in SaltStack.
Note VMware (The company I work for), bought SaltStack, so I don&amp;rsquo;t know, what the future plans look like, and if this is the correct way going forward, to do this kind of integration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docker for Almost Everything</title>
      <link>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2020-docker-for-almost-everything/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2020 19:26:12 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2020-docker-for-almost-everything/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m no expert in containers, but I do talk to a lot of admins in my job, that has not taken the time, to look at containers yet, and therefore haven&amp;rsquo;t found, if they can be a usefull tool, for them.
I think it has a lot to do, with containers, being something developers use, and all the talk around Kubernetes (K8S).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automating Folding@Home With VMware Code Stream</title>
      <link>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2020-automating-fah-with-cs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 16:42:22 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2020-automating-fah-with-cs/</guid>
      <description>I am always looking for new ways to do demo&amp;rsquo;s, and to showcase the solutions the company I work for have. One usecase, that I really wanted to show, was infrastructure as code (IAC), using a combination of both VMware and opensource tools. But not just as a deploy and destroy, but also as a way to maintain state in something that keeps running, and do the changes, from a source repository, like Github.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Move Blog</title>
      <link>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2020-move-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 12:56:48 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2020-move-blog/</guid>
      <description>For the last year or so, I have seen a lot of people, talking about their move of blogs, from a traditionel CMS system, to a static site.
I have had this on my todo, for quite some time, but I have also been quite satisfied, with blogger (my old blog hosting).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 11:56:57 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/about/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my little blog.
I&amp;rsquo;m not a big writer, so don&amp;rsquo;t exect much. But sometimes, I might create small posts, of what i&amp;rsquo;m doing, and what I think, others might find interesting.
Most of my time, is spend, changing from a Operations background, to learn a lot more around Development.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jenkins and CodeStream CSRF fix</title>
      <link>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2020-jenkins-and-codestream-csrf-fix/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 21:38:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2020-jenkins-and-codestream-csrf-fix/</guid>
      <description>For some time, I have had the problem with Jenkins, that when I ran my Code Stream pipeline, it gave me the following error 
To fix it, I have been running the code below, in the Jenkins &amp;ldquo;Script Console&amp;rdquo; import jenkins.model.Jenkins
def instance = Jenkins.instance
instance.setCrumbIssuer(null)
This has been ok, until my container, running Jenkins, restarted or got updated, and then I got the error again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Demo Enviroment on demand</title>
      <link>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2020-demo-enviroment-on-demand/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2020 12:25:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2020-demo-enviroment-on-demand/</guid>
      <description>A couple of years ago Jad El-Zein (@virtualjad) created a demo, where he ordered a VM (I think it was) using Siri on his iPhone, with vRealize Automation (VRA).
As a side project, to another thing, I&amp;rsquo;m working on, I thought I would recreate that demo, in a 2020 VRA Cloud version.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to show the value of Automation</title>
      <link>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2019-how-to-show-value-of-automation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 11:27:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2019-how-to-show-value-of-automation/</guid>
      <description>Being able to show the value, of automation is essential, to be able to keep getting support, for the time you spend on it.
One of my coworkers (Tore Brynaa) , gave me an idea, on how we could show that value back to the business, for the customers that have begun using vRealize Automation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Remote development from anywhere</title>
      <link>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2019-remote-development-from-anywhere/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 09:05:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2019-remote-development-from-anywhere/</guid>
      <description>VScode is that type of software, that I hated in the beginning, and now love (for the most part).
I have never been any good at coding, scripting etc. but the more my day job, exposes me to automation, the more I want to learn. And along with that, I found out, that VScode, was one of the thing, I better learn to love (or live with).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VMware Cloud Management series</title>
      <link>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2019-vmware-cloud-management-series/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2019 11:19:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2019-vmware-cloud-management-series/</guid>
      <description>I have started a new Cloud Management (CMP) series where I want to show, just how easy it is to get started at doing CMP.
It&amp;rsquo;s all in Danish, to keep it local, but I will will update this post, to keep all the videos in one place.
1. Multi Cloud Blueprints in Cloud Assembly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K8S Ingress and Pfsense firewall</title>
      <link>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2019-k8s-ingress-and-pfsense-firewall/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2019 15:04:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2019-k8s-ingress-and-pfsense-firewall/</guid>
      <description>I have been playing a bit with Kubernettes (K8S) lately.
Since it&amp;rsquo;s running on my vSphere environment, and not a public cloud, I don&amp;rsquo;t have native access to a load balancer, so I have to use the Ingress Controller instead.
Right now i&amp;rsquo;m using Rancher to deploy the K8S cluster, and due to lack of static ipadresses on my nodes, a LoadBalancer is not an easy thing to get working, it seams.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Duplicate ipadress on Packer Ubuntu VM&#39;s</title>
      <link>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2019-duplicate-ipadress-on-packer-ubuntu-vms/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 20:57:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2019-duplicate-ipadress-on-packer-ubuntu-vms/</guid>
      <description>After reading a blog post, from Cody&amp;rsquo;s blog thehumblelab.com, about how to create automated vSphere templates, using Packer.
I have been using it, for most of my vSphere templates in my demo lab at work.
But it has not been without problems. I have been having a problem with my Ubuntu templates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Password manager</title>
      <link>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2020-new-password-manager/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2019 13:44:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2020-new-password-manager/</guid>
      <description>I have been a (happy) long time user of Keepass.
It was the place to store passwords, notes etc, across many of the systems I use today.
That means mostly OSX, but also a bit Windows, and in some cases IOS as well.
The way I used it, was by having my kdb file, in a dropbox share, that I then accessed from all my devices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Filter Extensibility subscriptions in CAS</title>
      <link>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2019-filter-extensibility-subscriptions-in/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2019 13:28:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2019-filter-extensibility-subscriptions-in/</guid>
      <description>For the last couple of days, I have been playing quite a lot with Cloud Automation Services.
That means deploying a lot of VM&amp;rsquo;s, just to destroy them again.
Some time ago, I got help, from some good colleagues, to setup a Python Slack notification, using the extensibility on AWS Faas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloud Agnostic Blueprints in VMware CAS</title>
      <link>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2019-cloud-agnostic-blueprints-in-vmware-cas/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 07:51:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2019-cloud-agnostic-blueprints-in-vmware-cas/</guid>
      <description>VMware Cloud Automation Services went GA 2 days ago, on the 15/1/2019.
There is already a ton of blogs, describing the solution.
I thought that I would give my view on one of the things, that i find most cool about the solution.
Note that i&amp;rsquo;m no expert, but I already love the solution, and i&amp;rsquo;m looking forward to learning more about what I, and the customers I talk to, can do with it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting started with Cloud Automation Services - Almost</title>
      <link>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2018-getting-started-with-cloud-automation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2018 21:11:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2018-getting-started-with-cloud-automation/</guid>
      <description>I finally got started on Cloud Automation Services (CAS), or at least Cloud Assembly.
Living in Denmark, where many customers are talking Azure all the time, and the local vSphere environments, are smaller, the SAAS offering makes a lot of sense IMHO.
I must admit I already love the product, even thou it requires some learning, to get the hang of it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Homekit support for non homekit devices</title>
      <link>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2018-homekit-support-for-non-homekit-devices/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 08:58:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2018-homekit-support-for-non-homekit-devices/</guid>
      <description>For that last 2 years, I have been playing around with Home Automation.
So far i&amp;rsquo;m running a mix of both an Openhab installation, based on MQTT, and some Homekit devices (Philips hue etc).
Openhab is a great product, but I was finding myself, more and more, using Homekit, controlled from my ATV4, to be the way i do home automation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monitor Domain Admins using VMware Log Insight</title>
      <link>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2018-monitor-domain-admins-using-vmware-log/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 10:57:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2018-monitor-domain-admins-using-vmware-log/</guid>
      <description>I had a customer asking me yesterday, if it was possible to use Log Insight, to monitor changes done to the Domain Admins group.
An interesting use case, that i had not thought of before.
The answer is off course yes, so i thought i would write a small post about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloud Management Experience Day</title>
      <link>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2018-cloud-managent-experience-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2018 14:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2018-cloud-managent-experience-day/</guid>
      <description>A lot of my work time, these days, is spend on preparing a new thing we have in Denmark. It&amp;rsquo;s called Cloud Management Experience day.
We have already been running the same for VSAN, NSX and EUC.
The idea is to have customers participating in a full day og learning, where they can experience our products.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fingbox - New security device in my home</title>
      <link>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2018-fingbox-new-security-device-in-my-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 14:54:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2018-fingbox-new-security-device-in-my-home/</guid>
      <description>So i bought a new gadget. After hearing my collegaue, telling me about it, and I was sold.
Fing.io is a free network scanner app for IOS (and Android).
They extended it, by connecting it to a physical device, that connects to your router, and monitors your network.
It only need a cable in your router, and power, then you are done.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>vRealize Business - Do you know your cost ? </title>
      <link>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2018-vrealize-business-do-you-know-your-cost/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2018 09:05:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2018-vrealize-business-do-you-know-your-cost/</guid>
      <description>Do you know the cost of your datacenters, and what the cost would be, if you had to move your workloads to the public Cloud ?
One of the products, that can help with that, is VMware vRealize Business.
It&amp;rsquo;s probably one of the most overlooked products, in VMwares portfolio.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why i love my Netatmo Presence - Found potential thief</title>
      <link>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2018-why-i-love-my-netatmo-presence-found/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 13:57:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2018-why-i-love-my-netatmo-presence-found/</guid>
      <description>I love my Netatmo Presence. The reason is due to it&amp;rsquo;s abilities to detect different types of objects like cars, people, animals and other.
Due to that, I found that i had a visit, from somebody, who was probably trying to grab my bike, in the middle of the night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Auto Clean up old recordings</title>
      <link>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2018-auto-clean-up-old-recording/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2018 20:47:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2018-auto-clean-up-old-recording/</guid>
      <description>Some time ago, I bought the Netatmo Presence cam. I love the &amp;ldquo;Intelligence&amp;rdquo; in the cam (it detects different objects linke cars, people, animals), and it&amp;rsquo;s ability, to work when there is no wifi etc. due to the build in SD card.
I do however, upload everything to my NAS using ftp, for safe keeping.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data collection Catalog Item in VRA</title>
      <link>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2018-data-collection-catalog-item-in-vra/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2018 12:49:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2018-data-collection-catalog-item-in-vra/</guid>
      <description>One of the tasks, i often en up doing, when i work with vRealize Automation (vRA), is doing a catalog scan. The Catalog scan, checks for changes in my endpoints. This could be new templates, snapshots etc. hat i need in my blueprints.
To do this manually, you have to go to Infrastructure -&amp;gt; Compute Ressources -&amp;gt; Your endpoint -&amp;gt; Data collection -&amp;gt; Request now (under inventory).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VMware Lifecycle Manager - The first tool to install</title>
      <link>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2018-vmware-lifecycle-manager-first-tool-to/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2018 11:16:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2018-vmware-lifecycle-manager-first-tool-to/</guid>
      <description>VMware has released a new tool, to make it easyer to install and upgrade, some of your VMware products.
The product is called vRealize Suite Lifecycle manger, not to be mistaken for en earlier product VMware had, that was also called Lifecycle Manager.
The tool is fairly easy to install.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>vSphere HTML5 client - Have you tried the Fling ? </title>
      <link>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2017-vsphere-html5-client-have-you-tried/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2017 19:49:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.robert-jensen.dk/posts/2017-vsphere-html5-client-have-you-tried/</guid>
      <description>From time to time, people have asked me &amp;ldquo;When do you fix the vSphere web client&amp;rdquo;, or &amp;ldquo;When will the C# client come back&amp;rdquo;
Most of the time, people don&amp;rsquo;t know about VMware&amp;rsquo;s new HTML5 client, and have not tried it.
I must admit, that I loved the old C# client, and I had a hard time, converting to the flash Web client.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
